banderasnews.com 2002-12-05

# Privacy Policy

|  | **In The News!**  
---|---  
| **Local Events**  
| **Business & Technology**  
| **Real Estate**  
| **Destinations**  
| **Photo Galleries**  
  |   
| **Classified Ads**  
  |   
| **Profiles**  
| **Art Talk**  
| **Night Life**  
| **Community**  
| **Fishing Report**  
| **Health & Beauty**  
  |   
| **Web Archives**  
  |   
| **Humor**  
| **Comics**  
| **How To**  
| **Letters**  
| **Puzzler**  
| **Rumors**  
| **Ask Andy**  
| **Horoscope**  
  |   
| **Advertising**  
| **Shopping Guide**  
| **Ad Information**  
| **Print Distribution**  
  |   
  **Free Newsletter!**  
|  | 

**Privacy Statement**

* * *

 _ **BanderasNews.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our network of websites._

 **We use** your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address may be used to gather broad demographic information. Such information enables us to better tailor our content to our users needs and to help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience.

 **This site** contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

 **Advertising**  
This site may use the services of others for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, these services collect anonymous data typically through the use of cookies. Contact us to learn more about the use of these services.

 **Public Forums**  
This site may make forums, message boards, and/or newsgroups available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

 **Mailing List**  
This site maintains a newsletter mailing list. BanderasNews.com gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list at any time by following the instructions provided in every newsletter.

 **If you** have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this website, you can contact [Info@BanderasNews.com](mailto:Info@BanderasNews.com).
